Library of Congress and Fisk University Mississippi Delta collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts, 1939-1947
  - Correspondence, December 1942 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - From Benjamin A. Botkin to Jerome Sage, December 16, 1942
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - From Turner Johnson, Jr. to Alan Lomax, January 4, 1943
    - From Jim Henry to Alan Lomax, February 21, 1943
    - From Sid Hemphill to Alan Lomax, February 23, 1943
  - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - From Alan Lomax to Charles S. Johnson, January 2, 1947
    - From Alan Lomax to John W. Work, January 2, 1947
    - From John W. Work to Alan Lomax, December 28, 1947
    - From Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, January 2, 1948
  - Project planning documents, undated (Box-folder 1/24)
    Includes equipment lists, reading lists, reports, research materials, lists and forms.
  - Recording logs, original numbers, 1942 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Recording logs, AFS numbers, 1942 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Recording logs, concordance, 1942 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - Film logs, 1942 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Song lists by performer and topic, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Report on Preliminary Work in Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1941 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - List of Records on Machines in Clarksdale Amusement Places, September 1941 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Interview with S.L. Mangham, September 10, 1941 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Field Trip to Coahoma County, Mississippi, ca. 1942 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Accessions record, October 27, 1942 (Box-folder 1/34)
- Series II: Graphic Images, ca. 1942, 68 songs on 46 photostat sheets
  Song transcriptions by John W. Work
  - Ain't Goin’ Be Bad Blues / sung by “Son” House (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Blues (harmonica and voice) / sung and played by Turner Johnson (Box-folder 2/1)
  - All My Trouble Will Be Over / sung by Ella Williams (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Rock-a My Soul (Box-folder 2/1)
  - The Blind Man / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/1)
  - David / led by Rev. C. H. Savage (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Done Taken my Lord away / sung by Mrs. Mary Johnson, Lulu, Miss. (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Form the Line (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Go Loggy, Loggy, Loggy / led by Ruby Brown (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Four O'clock Blues / sung by Willie Blackwell (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Mississippi Blues / sung by William Brown (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Fox Hunters’ Song / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Get Right Church / sung by E. M. Martin and Willie Dale (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Levee Blues / sung by “Son” House (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Green Gravel / led by Ruby Smith (Box-folder 2/2)
  - The Late War / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/2)
  - All Power is in His Hands (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Here Come Two Gents from Holly Springs / sung by Ruby Harris and Ruby Hughes (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Daniel (Box-folder 2/2)
  - I'm Goin’ Let it Shine (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Red Wasp is Stingin’ Me (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Were marchin’ roun’ the levee / led by Sarah Lena Teague (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Holler by “Muddy Water” (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Levee Holler (Box-folder 2/3)
  - I Got a Bull Dog / sung by Houston Bacon (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Motherless Children Has a Hard Time (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Gonna Keep My Skillet Greasy / sung by Sid Hemphill (Box-folder 2/3)
  - I Got a Hiding Place / sung by the Holiness Church* (Box-folder 2/3)
  - I Got a Letter Blues / sung by Blind Lemon ? (Box-folder 2/3)
  - I Got on the Train / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/3)
  - I Heard the Voice of Jesus Say / “long meter” style of hymn sung by four Negro women of Hillhouse, Miss. (Box-folder 2/4)
  - I'm Going to Lean on the Lord / sung by Mrs. Roxie Threadgill (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Sorry, Sorry for to Leave You / sung by Mrs. Threadgill (Box-folder 2/4)
  - O Lord Will You Come by Here! (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Glory Hallelujah (Box-folder 2/4)
  - I'm Going to Stay on the Battlefield (Box-folder 2/4)
  - I'll Fly Away (Box-folder 2/4)
  - I Done Got Over (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Hallelu, Hallelu (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Moan (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Cryin’ “Holy Unto the Lord” / sung by Rev. E. N. Martin (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Hold the Wind / sung by Rev. E. N. Martin (Box-folder 2/4)
  - I'm Making to the City (harmonica and voice) / sung by Turner Johnson (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Late on the Evenin’ Blues / sung and played by “Muddy Water” (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Lining Railroad Track / dialogue and songs by Houston Bacon and Elias Boykin, 4 sheets (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Low Down the Chariot and Let Me Ride (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Needle Eye / led by Rosie Shelby (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Didee-o / led by Ruby Harris (Box-folder 2/5)
  - This is the Hammer / sung by Sid Hemphill (Box-folder 2/5)
  - No Condemnation / sung by the Holiness Church (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Sermon / John W. Work, 8 sheets (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Stagolee / sung by David Edward (Box-folder 2/6)
  - I'm Goin’ Keep My Skillet Greasy / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/6)
  - This Old Tampin’ / sung by Houston Bacon (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Stagolee / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Steal Away (voice and harmonica) / played and sung by Turner Junior Johnson (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Sittin’ on Top of the World (voice and harmonica / played and sung by Turner Junior Johnson (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Swing Down Chariot* / sung by the Mississippi Gospel Quartet (Box-folder 2/7)
  - These Days Got Ev’rybody Troubled / sung and composed by Charles Haffer, Jr. (Box-folder 2/7)
  - This Here's My Buryin’ Ground (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Calvary (Box-folder 2/7)
  - When I Lay This Burden Down (harmonica and voice) / sung and played by Turner Johnson (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Let Yo’ Heart (harmonica and voice) / sung and played by Turner Johnson (Box-folder 2/8)
  - When You Lose Your Money Learn to Lose / sung by Will Starks (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Willie Over the Water / led by Rosie Shelby (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Now Go on Down / led by Etherene Harris and Ann Williams (Box-folder 2/8)
  - You Got to Reap Your Own Damnation / sung by Mrs. Roxie Threadgill (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Rock Daniel / sung by Mrs. Roxie Threadgill (Box-folder 2/8)
  - You Pray on / sung by the Mississippi Gospel Quartet (Box-folder 2/8)
- Series III: Sound Recordings, 97 sound discs
  Approximately 37 .wav files were created from the sound discs (one file represents one side of a disc). Digital IDs indicate which discs have digital copies. All sound recordings also have preservation and reference copies on audiotape.
  - AFS 04757, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Rev. Ribbins and congregation and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. I'm Packing Up, Getting' Ready to Go, 1942
      - 2. Prayer, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Get Right with God, 1942
      - 2. Long Meter Hymn, 1942
      - 3. Presentation of Rev. Ribbins, 1942
  - AFS 04758, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Rev. Ribbins and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - Presentation of Rev. Ribbins (continued), 1942
    - Side B
      - Presentation of Rev. Ribbins (continued), 1942
  - AFS 04759, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. End of Sermon, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Calling the mourners, 1942
      - 2. Long Meter Hymn, 1942
      - 3. Mourners' Bench scene, 1942
      - 4. Soon One Morning, 1942
  - AFS 04760, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Prayers, mourning etc., 1942
      - 2. I'm Going Home on the Morning Train, 1942
      - 3. Minister talks about meeting, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Minister talks about meeting, 1942
      - 2. I'll be Waiting Up There, 1942
      - 3. I'll Fly Away, 1942
  - AFS 04761, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. I'm Gonna Stay on the Battlefield Till I Die, 1942
      - 2. Long meter hymn, 1942
      - 3. Long meter hymn. Announcement by deacon., 1942
      - 4. Long meter hymn. Announcement by deacon., 1942
    - Side B
      - Soon I'll Be at Home, 1942
        Performed by Negro Quartet.
  - AFS 04762 [Broken], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04763 [Broken], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04764 [Broken], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04765, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performer and location unidentified.
    - Side A
      - 2. Hallelu, Hallelu, 1942
  - AFS 04766, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performer unidentified; recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Samson, 1942
      - 2. O David, 1942
      - 3. I Know the Lord Will Fix a Way for Me, 1942
      - 4. I'm No Ways Worried, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Moaning, 1942
      - 2. Calvary, 1942
  - AFS 04767, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi. Side B location unidentified.
    - Side A
      - Farm economics (people speaking), 1942
    - Side B
      - No Good, undated
  - AFS 04768 [Missing], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04769, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Muddy Waters (McKinley Morganfield) and recorded by Alan Lomax and John W. Work in Stovall, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Country Blues, 1941
      - 2. I Be's Troubled, 1941
    - Side B
      - Blank
  - AFS 04770, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Burr Clove Blues, 1941
      - 2. Burr Clove Blues, 1941
    - Side B
      - 1. Country Blues, 1941
      - 2. I Be's Troubled, 1941
  - AFS 04771 [Missing], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04772, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Sermon, 1942
    - Side B
      - Sermon and singing, 1942
  - AFS 04773 [Missing], 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 04774, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and beginning of Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi. Side B Tracks 1-4 recorded by Alan Lomax at the Moorhead Plantation near Lula, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      Performer unidentified.
      - Singing, 1942
    - Side B
      - Singing (continued), 1942
      - 1. I Got a Hiding Place, 1941
        Performed by Congregation of the Church of God in Christ.
      - 2. No Condemnation, 1941
      - 3. Testimonials, 1941
      - 5. Build up a Building for the Lord, 1941
  - AFS 04775, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A recorded by Alan Lomax at the Moorhead Plantation near Lula, Mississippi. Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Testimonials (continued), 1941
      - 2. Sermon and song Standard for My King, 1941
      - 3. I'm Gonna Lift Up a Standard for My King, 1941
    - Side B
      - Sermon and singing (continued), 1942
  - AFS 04776, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Singing, 1942
    - Side B
      - Singing, 1942
  - AFS 04777, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis, 1942
    - Side B
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis (continued), 1942
  - AFS 04778, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis (continued), 1942
    - Side B
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis (continued), 1942
  - AFS 04779, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis (continued), 1942
    - Side B
      - Discussion about Jefferson Davis (continued), 1942
  - AFS 04780, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Son House, Fiddlin' Joe Martin, Leroy Williams, and Willie Brown and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Guitar tuning, 1942
      - 2. Levee Camp Blues, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Government Fleet Blues, 1942
      - 2. Walking Boss, 1942
  - AFS 04781, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Son House, Fiddlin' Joe Martin, Leroy Williams, and Willie Brown and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Lake Coromant, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Shetland Pony Blues
      - 2. Fo' Clock Blues
      - 3. Make Me a Pallet on the Floor
    - Side B
      - 1. Camp Hollers
      - 2. Delta Blues
      - 3. Going to Fishing
  - AFS 04782, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Leroy Williams, Willie Brown, E. C. (Estil Cortez) Ball and Mrs. Ball; recording location unidentified.
    - Side A
      - 1. Test
      - 2. Test
      - 3. Uncle Sam Done Called
    - Side B
      - 1. Drunkard's Special
      - 2. Unidentified?
      - 3. Jinny Jenkins
  - AFS 06109, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by the Nashville Washboard band and recorded by Alan Lomax and John Work at Work's home in Nashville, Tennessee.
    - Side A
      - 1. Deary Don't Be Angry, July 15, 1942
      - 2. Kohoma Blues, July 15, 1942
      - 3. I'll Be Glad When You're Dead, You Rascal You, July 15, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Goin' Away to Make It Lonesome Here, July 15, 1942
      - 2. Soldier's Joy, July 15, 1942
        With James Kelly on mandolin.
      - 3. Arkansas Traveler, July 15, 1942
      - 4. Old Joe, July 15, 1942
  - AFS 06604, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Tracks 1-7 on Side A recorded by Alan Lomax and John Work at Work's home in Nashville, Tennessee. Track 8 on Side A and Side B recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs6604a
      - 1. Washboard solo, breakdown tempo, June 1942
        Performed by the Nashville Washboard band.
      - 2. Washboard solo, blues tempo, June 1942
      - 3. Washboard solo, swing tempo, June 1942
      - 4. Washboard solo, swing tempo, June 1942
      - 5. Washboard solo, breakdown tempo, June 1942
      - 6. Bull fiddle tuning and interview, June 1942
      - 7. Bull fiddle tuning and interview, June 1942
      - 8. Opening announcement, July 25, 1942
        Performed by the Silent Grove Baptist Church.
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs6604b
      - 1. Dr. Watts Hymn, July 25, 1942
      - 2. Prayer by minister, July 25, 1942
      - 3. Announcement, July 25, 1942
      - 4. I'll Fly Away, July 25, 1942
      - 5. Use Me, My Lawd, Use Me (Jubilee Quartet), July 25, 1942
  - AFS 06605, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax at Sadie Beck's Plantation in Arkansas.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs6605a
      - 1. Four O'Clock Flower Blues, June 1942
        Performed by Willie Blackwell with William Brown.
      - 2. Interview with Willie Blackwell, June 1942
      - 3. Junion, a Jap's Girl Christmas for his Santa Claus, June 1942
      - 4. Blank
  - AFS 06606, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and Side B Track 1 recorded by Alan Lomax at Sadie Beck's Plantation in Arkansas. Side B Track 2 recorded by Alan Lomax at Robinsonville, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs6606a
      Performed by William Brown.
      - 1. Mississippi Blues, June 1942
      - 2. East St. Louis Blues, June 1942
      - 3. Ragged and Dirty, June 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs6606b
      - 1. This World Is Gone to Destruction, June 1942
        Performed by James Moore, W.H. Brooks, Rufus Murphy, Tommy Hacket, and William Brown
      - 2. Special Rider Blues, July 17, 1942
        Performed by Son House.
  - AFS 06607, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Son House and recorded by Alan Lomax at Robinsonville, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs6607a
      - 1. Low Down, Dirty Dog Blues, July 17, 1942
      - 2. Depot Blues, July 17, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. American Defense, July 17, 1942
      - 2. Am I Right or Wrong, July 17, 1942
      - 3. Walking Blues, July 17, 1942
  - AFS 06608, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and Side B Track 1 recorded by Alan Lomax at Robinsonville, Mississippi. Side B Tracks 2 and 3 recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. County Farm Blues, July 17, 1942
      - 2. The Pony Blues, July 17, 1942
      - 3. The Jinx Blues (incomplete), July 17, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. The Jinx Blues, July 17, 1942
      - 2. Meet Me in Jerusalem, 1942
        Performed by Turner Junior Johnson.
      - 3. When I Lay My Burden, 1942
  - AFS 06609, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Turner Junior Johnson and recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Sweet Lamb of God, 1942
      - 2. Preacher Let your Heart Catch on Fire, 1942
      - 3. In New Jerusalem, 1942
      - 4. Steal Away, 1942
      - 5. Travelin' On, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. The Buzzard Eats the Rabbit (folk tale), 1942
      - 2. The Hawk and the Buzzard, 1942
      - 3. Sitting on Top of the World, 1942
      - 4. Minglewood Blues, 1942
  - AFS 06610, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by David "Honeyboy" Edwards and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Coahoma County, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, 1942
      - 2. Spread My Raincoat Down (blues), 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, 1942
      - 2. You Got to Roll (chain gang song), 1942
      - 3. You Got to Roll (chain gang song), 1942
      - 4. Stagolee, 1942
      - 5. Just a Spoonful, 1942
  - AFS 06611, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. I love My Jelly Roll, 1942
      - 2. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, 1942
      - 3. Hellatakin' Blues, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, 1942
      - 2. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, 1942
  - AFS 06612, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and Side B Tracks 1-3 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side B Tracks 4-5 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Friars Pt., Mississippi.
    - Side A
      Performed by David "Honeyboy" Edwards.
      - 1. Worried Life Blues, June 20, 1942
      - 2. Watercoast Blues, June 20, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. The Army Blues, June 20, 1942
      - 2. Tear it Down, June 20, 1942
      - 3. Ragtime selection, June 20, 1942
      - 4. Near the Cross, July 20, 1942
        Performed by the Friendly Five Harmony Singers.
      - 5. Tossed and Driven, July 20, 1942
  - AFS 06613, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by the Friendly Five Harmony Singers and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Friars Pt., Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. There's No Grave can Hold My Body Down, July 20, 1942
      - 2. Speech by the President of the Quartet, July 20, 1942
      - 3. Get Away, Jordan, July 20, 1942
      - 4. I Believe the Good Old Bible from the Beginning to the End, July 20, 1942
      - 5. I Thank the Lord I'm in His Care, July 20, 1942
    - Side B
      - Blank
  - AFS 06614, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by David "Honeyboy" Edwards and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Delta Tourist Camp, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - Toasts, folk tales and interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, July 22, 1942
    - Side B
      - Toasts, folk tales and interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, July 22, 1942, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
  - AFS 06615
    - Side A
      - 1. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, July 22, 1942
      - 2. Interview with David "Honeyboy" Edwards, July 22, 1942
      - 3. Do You Want a Little Bit of This (game song), July 22, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Test, July 22, 1942
      - 2. Test, July 22, 1942
      - 3. Wind Howlin' Blues, July 22, 1942
      - 4. Roamin' and Ramblin' Blues, July 22, 1942
  - AFS 06616, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by a congregation and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Coahoma County, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. At the Cross, 1942
      - 2. Prayer, 1942
      - 3. When I Can Read My Promise Clear, 1942
      - 4. Prayer with humming, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Sermon (first part distorted), 1942
      - 2. Commencement of prayer, 1942
        Spoken by J.H. Whiting.
  - AFS 06617, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Prayer after the sermon, 1942
      - 2. Take My Hand, Precious Lord, Lead Me On, 1942
      - 3. Announcement, 1942
      - 4. Talk on Unity, 1942
        Spoken by Rev. H.F. Richardson
  - AFS 06618, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Talk on Unity (continued), 1942
      - 2. Prayer, 1942
      - 3. One Little Talk with Jesus Makes it All Right, 1942
        Spoken by L. M. McNeal and J. H. Haley
    - Side B
      - 1. Fragment of a talk by Rev., 1942
      - 2. Various announcements, 1942
      - 3. Long Meter Hymn, 1942
  - AFS 06619, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Missionary prayer, 1942
        Spoken by H.T. James.
      - 2. Missionary sermon, 1942
        Spoken by J. W. Terrell.
    - Side B
      - 1. Missionary sermon (continued), 1942
      - 2. Missionary sermon (continued), 1942
      - 3. Missionary sermon (continued), 1942
  - AFS 06620, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      Spoken by J. W. Terrell
      - Missionary sermon (continued), 1942
    - Side B
      Spoken by J.H. Haley.
      - Closing prayer, 1942
  - AFS 06621, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by E. M. Martin and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Nelson Funeral Home in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Test
      - 2. Test
      - 3. Test
      - 4. Test
      - 5. Just a Closer Walk with Thee, 1942
      - 6. Be Holy unto the Lord (Woe Be Unto You), 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Hold the Wind, 1942
      - 2. Hold the Wind (continued), 1942
  - AFS 06622, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Nelson Funeral Home in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - Interview with Charles Haffer, Jr., July 23, 1942
    - Side B
      - Interview with Charles Haffer, Jr. (continued), July 23, 1942
  - AFS 06623, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Charles Haffer, Jr., and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Nelson Funeral Home in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - These Days Got Everybody Troubled, July 23, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Interview with Charles Haffer, Jr., July 23, 1942
      - 2. The Natchez Theatre Fire Disaster, July 23, 1942
  - AFS 06624, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      Performed by Charles Haffer, Jr.
      - 1. A Song of the Great Disaster (Storm of '42), July 23, 1942
      - 2. I'll Be Glad to See the Son When He Come, July 23, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Where Shall I Be When The First Trumpet Sound?, July 23, 1942
        Performed by E. M. Martin and Pearline Johns.
      - 2. I'm Going Home on the Morning Train, July 23, 1942
      - 3. A Charge to Keep I Have a God to Glorify, July 23, 1942
        Performed by E.M. Martin and Willie Dale Byrd.
  - AFS 06625, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Must Jesus Bear the Cross Alone, July 23, 1942
      - 2. Must Jesus Bear the Cross Alone, July 23, 1942
      - 3. Funeral customs, July 23, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Funeral customs (continued), July 23, 1942
      - 2. Job, a memorial sermon, July 23, 1942
  - AFS 06626, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Job, a memorial sermon (continued), July 23, 1942
        Performed by E. M. Martin.
    - Side B
      - 1. Opening routine in show (story), July 23, 1942
        Performed by M.C. Orr.
      - 2. The Ugliest Animal, the Baboon (story), July 23, 1942